thrillcall.com 2012-12-26

# Find concerts, tour dates, and concert tickets at Thrillcall

The Thrillcall music discovery, concert listing and social networking service allows a User (together the "User", "they" and "you") to discover, listen and see different forms of music related media, including music, video, photos and text while enabling Users to interact and express their opinions with other Users (the "Service"). 316 Ventures, Inc. operates the Thrillcall service and the Thrillcall.com website (together the "Service", "We", the "Company" and "Thrillcall"). We understand that your privacy is very important. Our privacy policy explains how we gather and use information while safeguarding your privacy.

##  _Consent_

By using Thrillcall, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy and the Thrillcall Terms of Use. By disclosing any information through the Service, you consent to the collection, storage and use of such information by Thrillcall as set out in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If Thrillcall makes any changes to this Privacy Policy these changes will be detailed on this page in order to ensure that you are aware of what information is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances it will be disclosed. If you are concerned about how your information is collected, used or disclosed, you should periodically check review this Privacy Policy. If you have any specific concerns not addressed in the Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@thrillcall.com.

##  _Personal Information_

When a User registers with Thrillcall, they create their own profile. User profile information, as well as a User's name, email, photo and other personal information, may be displayed to users of the Thrillcall service to enable you to connect with people on the Service.

  * **User Provided Information** : For visitors to the website and registered Users, we log standard technical information, such as an IP address. If a User chooses to register with Thrillcall, the User will need to provide a valid email address and birth date. The User will also be required to select a User ID and password. In addition, Thrillcall may ask the User to provide a valid physical address and other demographic information, such as gender, interests or occupation. For the purchase of products and services, credit card and billing information, for verification purposes, may be required. Thrillcall may collect other personal information from time to time, such as when Users provide feedback, comments or communicate with others through the Service. 
  * **Cookies** : Thrillcall uses cookies, small text files containing a string of characters, to operate its website and provide a personalized User experience. Thrillcall uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain after a User closes the particular web browser used to access the Service. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by using the mechanisms in a web browser. A browser's help function should explain this process. Users have the option to set their web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Thrillcall service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 
  * **Log File Information** : When you use the Thrillcall service, our servers automatically record certain information that a User's web browser sends whenever they visit the website. These server logs may include information such as your web request; Internet Protocol ("IP") address, this may or may not be associated with a particular Internet Service Provider (ISP); browser type; browser language; referring pages and URL, exit pages and associated URLs; platform type; number of clicks; domain names; landing pages; pages viewed and the order of those pages; the amount of time spent on particular pages and the web site; the date and time of your request; content play information as well as other information. Thrillcall may use one or more cookies to uniquely identify a User's browser. 
  * **Address Book Email Addresses** : If a User chooses to use the Service's invitation application to contact and invite one of your personal contacts or friends (a "Friend") to the Service site, Thrillcall will ask the User for information needed to send the invitation, such as an email address and password. Thrillcall will automatically send your Friend an email or instant message inviting them to visit the site. Thrillcall stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a Friend connection if a User's invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. 

##  _Use of Information_

The information Thrillcall collects about Users over time is used to provide the Service. Thrillcall may utilize demographic, location and other information to create a database of User profiles, program content or advertisements based on User information and for marketing analysis among other purposes. In addition, Thrillcall may utilize technical information to diagnose technical issues with the Service and to operate the Thrillcall.com web site. Thrillcall may utilize User information to improve the products and services offered to Users.

Search results in the Thrillcall Service are personally generated by Users and are based not only on User inputs but may also be based on what is popular among the broader community of Users as well as individual User interests such as a User's profile, advertisements and promotions, groups a User has joined, and what other Users, particularly those Users with whom an individual User has established contact with, have expressed interest in. Data about searches and search results may be maintained by Thrillcall to help improve the Service.

Thrillcall may use information in a User's profile without identifying a User as an individual to third parties. Thrillcall may use this information for numerous purposes such as aggregating how many people in a group or community like a band and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that the Service can provide you with a more customized experience.

Invitations and messages are sent via email, instant messaging, message boards, postings, comments, mobile phone messaging and other means on the User's behalf by Thrillcall ("User Messages"). If a User invites another person to join the Thrillcall Service, Thrillcall will ask for that person's name and online contact information. Thrillcall stores this information and uses it to contact and inform that person they have been invited to join the Thrillcall Service. Thrillcall may send reminders to the people that Users choose to invite.

When Users communicate with other individuals on the Service utilizing User Messages, Thrillcall will attempt to authenticate Users. However, as Thrillcall does not control the technology or communications services utilized by User Messages, Thrillcall can only attempt authentication.

You may post User Content (as defined in the Thrillcall Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Please note that all personal information a User displays or communicates using a User Messages functionality becomes public information and Thrillcall is not responsible for any information a User chooses to make public. Thrillcall may monitor, at its discretion, such traffic via electronic software or otherwise in order to check for obscenity, defamation or abusive language, which Thrillcall reserves the right to remove at any time. In addition, if a User chooses to personally communicate or meet with any other Thrillcall User by exchanging postal/email addresses, telephone numbers or otherwise via the interactive functionality of the Service, a User does so at their own risk. Thrillcall cannot be held responsible for any consequences which flow from a User's decision to communicate or interact with other Thrillcall Users in places or under circumstances which Thrillcall does not control. Thrillcall advises Users to use extreme caution whenever they socialize or interact with people whom they have met via the internet.

##  _Information Protection_

Thrillcall's computers store User account information, and may cache User profile information for backup purposes. Thrillcall employs the following industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control:

  * Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information.
  * Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as email addresses and User names.
  * Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do.
  * Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information

Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Thrillcall cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, Thrillcall cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. Thrillcall is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

##  _When Thrillcall Discloses Information_

Thrillcall may share personally identifiable information about our Users with third parties, including: (1) with a User's consent or following the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out for specific programs, advertisements or features, or (2) when Thrillcall has a good faith belief that it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (3) to process payments for products or services; (4) as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (5) where required by law; or (6) at Thrillcall's sole discretion, where Thrillcall deems necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Thrillcall employees, contractors or other agents or any third party. Thrillcall shares non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous Log File information) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for our service.

In the event of a change of ownership or a direct merger with or acquisition by another entity, User information may be transferred to the acquiring entity. Users have the ability and control to remove or alter account specific information at any time.

##  _Third Parties/Advertisers and Your Information_

Thrillcall may provide links to third party websites or allow other companies, called third-party ad servers, to display advertisements to Users. Ad server companies may receive your IP address and can write and read their own cookies on a User's computer, just as if a User had requested a web page from the ad server website. Thrillcall is not responsible for, and does not have any control over, the privacy practices or the content of such third parties or how they treat information about their Users. Thrillcall encourages Users to read the privacy policies of any website visited to find out how they are treating your personal information. For more information about how to "opt-out" of cookies from certain of our ad serving partners, please click here.

Thrillcall will not provide contact information to third party marketers without a User's permission. Thrillcall shares your information with third parties when we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the Service; we are legally required to do so or; when permitted by the User.

Thrillcall may provide information to service providers to help us provide the Service. Specifically, Thrillcall may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email about or for Thrillcall, to remove repetitive information from our User lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where the Service utilizes third parties for the processing of any personal information, Thrillcall will implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Thrillcall specified purposes.

Please note that information stored or cached on other Users' computers is subject to those Users' security practices, which are beyond Thrillcall's control. Although Thrillcall makes good faith efforts to store information collected or stored by Thrillcall in a secure manner, Thrillcall cannot guarantee complete security. Information held by Thrillcall will be maintained for a length of time appropriate to the Company's business needs.

##  _User Options and Responsibilities_

User profiles contain information about individual Users that those Users may want to share with other Users. Protecting the privacy of your profile is each individual User's responsibility. Thrillcall cautions you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, or driver's license numbers) with other Users or place such information in a User profile.

Any information a User chooses to display on the Thrillcall Service, including a User profile, will be viewable by the entire World Wide Web. For every User's safety, Thrillcall cautions all Users not to include home addresses, telephone numbers or any other personal information that could allow strangers to contact a User outside of the Thrillcall service.

To maintain privacy, it is also important not to share a User password with anyone. Selecting a longer password with a mix of letters, numbers and symbols helps to make guessing a User password more difficult. It is also helpful to change passwords on a regular basis.

It is each User's individual responsibility to select the desired privacy setting upon creation of an account or registering with the Thrillcall Service. Upon registering with the Thrillcall service, some privacy settings items may have a default privacy setting so that a degree of privacy protection is selected. In this case, it is the User's responsibility to understand the associated privacy setting before creating content to ensure the handling of a User's information meets their individual expectations.

A User may choose to correct or update the information they have submitted to Thrillcall by editing their User profile or account information. If a User removes your information, it may continue to persist on back-up media.

##  _Safe Use of Thrillcall_

To report violations of the Thrillcall Terms of Use, improper account use, or identity theft please refer to the Thrillcall Terms of Use. For general information for Users and parents about staying safe on Thrillcall, here are some websites with valuable information:

  * Wiredsafety.org
  * Commonsense.com
  * Ncmec.org
  * Blogsafety.org
  * OnguardOnline.gov

##  _Policy for Young People's Privacy_

Thrillcall complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Thrillcall or send any information about yourself to Thrillcall, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Thrillcall. In the event that Thrillcall learns that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, Thrillcall will attempt to delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that Thrillcall might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@Thrillcall.com. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.

Thrillcall recommends that young people between the ages of 13 and 18 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. Thrillcall strongly encourages parents to supervise children when online. Thrillcall therefore recommend that parental control tools be put in place.

##  _Notice to International Users_

Thrillcall.com is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Thrillcall service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Thrillcall service, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

##  _Changes and Updates_

Your use of Thrillcall, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. Thrillcall reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. If Thrillcall makes any substantive changes to our policies, we will notify registered Users by either posting bulletins on the Thrillcall service, by email at the address provided by a User, or by posting notice of changes within the Privacy Policy. Each individual's continued use of the Thrillcall Service, Thrillcall.com or any Thrillcall software after the changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes a User's agreement with such changes with regard to information collected from Users in the past and in the future.

##  _Contacting Us/Enforcement_

If a User has any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Thrillcall, or an experience with Thrillcall.com, please contact us at:

Thrillcall.com.   
Customer Service - Privacy Issues   
332 Pine St.   
San Francisco, CA 94104   
info@thrillcall.com 

Revised October 22, 2008
